To compete， I needed to get around
the fact that I didn't want it
to be this big thing，
so I basically just rolled up
with a hat and sunglasses，
and I was wearing a COVID mask.
And I registered under my first
and middle name， so Mark Elliott.
And it wasn't until I actually pulled
all that stuff off right before
I got on the mat
that I think people knew it was me.
So it was pretty low key.
- But you're still a public figure.
- Yeah， I mean， I didn't wanna lose.
- Right， the thing you're partially afraid
of is not just the losing，
but being almost like embarrassed.
It's so raw， the sport， in that like，
it's just you and another human being.
There's a primal aspect there.
- Oh， yeah its perfect.
- For a lot of people， it can be terrifying，
especially the first time
you're doing the competing，
and it wasn't for you.
I see the look of excitement in your face.
It wasn't， no fear.
- I just think part of learning is failing.
The main thing， people who train jiu-jitsu，
it's like you need to not have pride
because I mean all the stuff
that you were talking
about before about， you know，
getting choked or getting， you know，
a joint lock.
It's um， you only get
into a bad situation
if you're not willing to tap
once you've already lost right?
And， but obviously
when you're getting started
with something， you're not gonna be
an expert at it immediately.
So you just need to be willing
to go with that.
But I think this is like， I don't know，
I mean， maybe I've just been
embarrassed enough times in my life.
I do think
that there's a thing where like，
you know， as people grow up，
maybe they don't wanna be embarrassed
or anything.
They've built their adult identity
and they kind of have a sense
of who they are
and what they want to project
and I don't know.
I think maybe to some degree.
You know your ability
to keep doing interesting things
is your willingness to be embarrassed
again and go back to step one
and start as a beginner
and get your **** kicked
and you know look stupid doing things，
and yeah I think so many of the things
that we're doing
whether it's whether it's this.
I mean this is just like a kind
of a physical part of my life，
but but it running the company
it's like we just take on
new adventures and， you know，
all the big things that we're doing
I think of is like 10 plus year missions
that we're on where you think
of as like 10 plus year missions
that we're on where often early on，
people doubt that we're gonna be able
to do it and the initial work
seems kind of silly and our whole ethos
is we don't wanna wait，
until something is perfect
to put it out there.
We wanna get it out quickly
and get feedback on it.
And so I don't know， I mean，
there's probably just something
about how I approach things in there.
But I just kind of think
that the moment that you decide
that you're gonna be too embarrassed
to try something new，
then you're not gonna
learn anything anymore.